Behold,
the village of Windnight's Lot, nestled
in a valley and ringed by daunting cliffs.
A castle dominates the landscape,
built in the Middle Ages as
a proving ground for knights.
It houses prisoners who toil underground,
mining coal as pennants for their crimes.
Fishing and farming provide
sustenance and commerce alike.
Five hundred and seventeen souls
call the sleepy bird their home.
But how few shall remain
when the carnage is done?
Thank you for listening.
Kinoto!
Farmers sing to the harvest.
Thus far, all is well.
However, Dio lurks in the
shadows waiting to strike.
What happened?
Well, Speedwagon has been begging
me to share in your power.
I meant to help him create
just a little bit of harmone,
as I did that first day with you.
It seems I was too rough.
Did my finger slip?
Un miliai, you're discusi,
my dear Speedwagon.
In English, please!
El culprit is a lad, it would seem.
His crime was well planned.
I salute the boy's ingenuity.
How come you two are heaping
praise on that little imp?
He's making off with every
pound we have to our names.
Oi, bring it back!
Yes, he took our money.
But think how he might be able to help.
Agreed.
A guide who knows the lay of
the land would not be unwelcome.
Um... Yeah!
What the...?
He's walking on it!
Jojo, your shoes are getting wet.
Try to bolster your haamon
for the sake of your wardrobe.
Ah, that was a nice diminuendo.
Your overdrive passed through
the rocks as smooth as silk.
Do you think I struck
the right spot, Baron?
No, but a couple of paces
to the left should do it.
Two pounds says I'm right.
What?
It shocked me!
Molto Bone.
What happened? Who are you?
Why are you holding me?
Lad, are you all right?
The force shouldn't have
hurt you that badly.
Did I use too much hormone?
I'd guess we were meant to give chase
when he took our bag. Look around.
This is a graveyard!
It's no accident that we now find
ourselves held by these restless cadavers,
my friends.
Our young thief, he was hypnotized and made
to lure us here. There, Jojo! It's him!
Huh?
The sun is gone.
You will not live to
see it rise once more.
Dio!
Why are they crawling out?
I've been trying to steal my spine
leading up to this little tete-a-tete,
but it's like the Grim Reaper's
breathing down me neck.
I'm all a sweat.
How am I supposed to find my courage when
that monster's staring right at us, huh?
Sir Joestar loved him, and all he
got for his troubles was death.
Listen, you.
You're gonna pay for it.
This is Dio Brando.
He and his minions have no power to
attack us while we stand in the daylight,
but here in a field of
darkness and carrion?
He thinks us easy prey
ripe for the taking at any
moment a creature of such
guile must not have the mask!
Somehow we will purge
the world of this evil.
What do they call you that?
Poco?
Well, Poco, hang on tight.
It's time for us to go.
Jojo, this way! Lead on!
Zoom punch!
Dio Brando.
Jojo and Speedwagon have told me much.
To the mask that allows you to act
out your evil heart, I say only this.
This time, I break you.
Hey, bambino!
It's easy to be cocky when you're
up there out of harm's way.
Come and fight!
You dare to address me thus, insect.
I, the pinnacle of creation.
To mere humans, I am like unto a god.
So why would I cavort down
in the filth with you?
Me almost knocked me off my
feet with a blast of pure hate.
Already this Dio has the soul of a tyrant.
All of the scars from my
battle with Jojo have healed.
All save this one.
Come, Charlatan.
Relinquish your blood, that I
may erase this imperfection.
Tell me, to undo your injuries, how
many innocent lives did you consume?
I don't know.
How many loaves of bread have
you eaten in your lifetime?
What are you doing?
I will take him home!
Your doom is nigh, Dio!
Hail!
Solar Hormone, pierce the night!
Sunlight, yellow, overdrive!
He did it!
His Hormone is moving its way up Diozor!
Consider this an eclipse.
Your hand!
It's freezing me!
It's simple, really.
For Hamon to work, blood must flow
through this arm with which you hit me.
I froze the very blood in your veins,
rendering your attack powerless.
I have mastery of my body in ways
that you can't even begin to dream.
You see, I just vaporized
the moisture in my left arm.
The force of it pulled in
all heat in the immediate
area freezing your arm
in the process and now?
Time for the coup de grace!
This punch is going to shatter your
arm and your skull like a windowpane!
Think again!
I'm ending your reign
of terror here and now!
Your blood I can feel the
evil coursing through it.
Stop it.
You're going to set me all a-tremble.
Masterful block by the by.
For the moment, your mentor lives.
I didn't think you had it in you. Jojo!
That said, if you keep cutting in like
this, I'm liable to lose my temper.
Terra, now!
It's useless! Yes!
As you can see, by freezing my arm,
your puny attack had nowhere to go.
If you think Hamon will save
you, you are sorely mistaken.
His strength is like
nothing I've ever witnessed.
This fiend is our equal many times over.
Wait, he's about to freeze
Jojo's arm, just like mine!
Come what may, I can't
let harm before the lad!
Barron Zeppeli!
Tor, this ain't happening!
My hand's cold as ice.
Every nerve is crying out in pain.
The skin on my fingers is peeling.
He removed the moisture.
The Baron's arm is in a pretty bad way.
Gangrene will take it if we
don't get the blood flowing.
What do we do?
Homo's the only weapon in our arsenal.
How do we stand against him?
So anemic, this parlor trick of yours.
You should save your breath.
Is it an earthquake?
You're going to need that air for all
the screaming I have in store for you.
Tarkus! Blueford!
Arise and fight at my command!
Let their cries of anguish resound,
so that all may know my glory!
Where'd he take up these bruises?
Poco, get to safety!
These are knights,
casualties of Queen Elizabeth's fatal
machinations in the mid-1500s against Mary,
Queen of Scotland.
Heed me well.
I find these humans vexing.
I order you to destroy them.
I care not how.
Tell me I'm dreaming!
That big one broke the
boulder with a single finger!
They are waiting for Jojo.
He's their main target.
He's a warrior, but he
can't handle both of them.
If only my blood would
start moving a little bit.
Then what, Baron?
Then I could heal my arm
a little with Harmon.
How am I supposed to thaw
this damnable thing in time?
If it's heat you need, Speedwagon's
feeling right charitable this evening.
What?
So you have a plan, then?
In a pinch I figured this'll do ya!
You selfless idiot!
Heard they treat frostbite in
the arctic by cutting open a
seal and sticking the frozen hand
a foot into the poor blighter!
Zoom punch! Aye, pest!
Give me your blood!
His hair!
He's using it to feed on me!
Speedwagon, you don't have to do this.
With all due respect,
I'd be buggered before I let harm come
to you or Jojo while I can lend a hand.
If he can drink my blood through this,
then perhaps it will serve as a
conduit for my hormone as well.
Sunlight yellow overdrive!
Nothing happened.
Have I already lost too much vitality
to make my hormone effective?
I may have sold you short, Amico.
I thought you would run
when things got truly dire.
Me despiace.
Baron, if we live through this,
you and me are right as rain.
I need to get my arm working.
There's no way he can take them alone.
Highballing that sword freezes
me up worse than you just did.
Jojo's well over six feet tall, but next
to that thingy might as well be Tom Thumb.
Look at the face on
that one, and that one!
He's the bleeding minotaur!
I can read people like a book, and
these two are full-a-story speed wagon?
don't want to hear, thank you kindly.
You should be honored to perish at the
hands of these men, Tarkus and Bluford.
Bow to my will, O warriors of yore.
In the mid-16th century, two women
waged war for the Crown of England.
the cunning Queen Elizabeth I, a Tudor,
and the beautiful Mary
Stuart, Queen of Scots.
The most steadfast of her vassals were
the great knights Tarkus and Bluford.
They had lost their families, without a
purpose to center them, a raison d 'etre.
They were adrift.
The dutiful man seeks respite,
not in the vagaries of romance,
but in something larger and ineffable.
In Mary they found just that.
They swore to serve and honor the young
queen, even at the cost of their own lives.
But one day, Mary's husband,
Lord Darnley, was found murdered.
Seeing a chance to strike, Elizabeth
blamed Mary for Darnley's death.
The people turned against Mary.
She was caught and imprisoned
in a series of castles.
Tarkus and Bluford fought like
lions to free their queen.
So fearsome were they, Elizabeth
approached them with a bargain.
Surrender and bring an
end to this bloodshed.
Grant us but this one thing
and we will spare Mary's life.
If our lives can buy the
Queen her freedom, I accept!
I've no regrets.
They went to Elizabeth
and sealed their fate.
You think you're so selfless, don't you?
Well, you're losing
your hands for nothing.
Your precious Mary's already worm food?
Go ahead, take a look over by that
wall if you're having your doubts.
Not so royal now, is she?
Elizabeth, you serpent!
You played us false and
murdered Mary anyway!
I die this day, but my hatred for you and
your wretched family will live forever!
Curse is on you, Queen!
And thus, they went to their end.
Legend has it that Tarukas'
neck was stiff with fury,
and the headsman broke many an axe
before the task was finally done.
For his part,
Bluford's hair coiled around
the executioner's feet,
the peerless locks
slicing the man's flesh.
The story of these brave knights' betrayal
seems to have struck a chord with me.
From the earth I called them to wreak
their vengeance all these centuries later.
Such is the power at my command.
In life they were fearsome.
In death they are invincible.
We have sworn fealty to Lord Dio.
We have come to lay waste to this world.
It is a place without redemption.
That hate they felt when they
died, it had 300 years to ferment.
Dio's turned the flower of
knighthood into vengeful monsters.
Keep your wits about you, Jojo.
Hormone within me, come to my aid!
Scarlet Overdrive!
Look at that power!
He looks so calm, but I know
they ain't far from his thoughts.
All that he's lost, and
what he's rediscovered.
Godspeed, you brave bastard!
Methinks this boy is
a champion of his day.
He shall make the perfect target upon
which to practice the art of war.
This one's flesh belongs to me.
Oh, yes.
I can smell his delicious
cartilage already. Another zombie?
He is our foe.
Get thee gone from here, you gluttony.
He moves with infernal speed.
Milord Dio, in this young man I do
sense a great reservoir of spirit.
I humbly petition you for the right to face
him in soul combat and strike him down.
As you will then.
Tarkus, this one here's mine.
That's Bluford the Black Knight.
He was known to be a flawless fighter
and he was utterly devoid of mercy.
Just watching him put one
foot in front of the other,
I can tell he's no one to tangle with.
Back in my school days, we learned
about this man, he and Tarkus.
And now, he returns from
the dead to kill me?
Relax your muscles, Jojo.
Breathe steadily, no matter what!
What's this?
He's got both hands behind his back!
Bluford is giving nothing away!
Which one is his sword arm?
Neither.
His hair wields the blade.
No, but...
You've a keen eye, my boy.
My hair's dance macabre has
claimed many. Have at thee!
Shoujo!
Oh no!
He's at a serious disadvantage.
No air to breathe means no harmone.
We have to help him.
What now, this brute?
Damn, he needs us.
And we can't lift a finger to save him.
Hmph.
Jojo's as good as dead.
He can't touch Blueford underwater.
I will go.
Here, there is nothing left to see.
And now, I will transform this
sleepy village into a necropolis!
The zombies I create will devour England
like a plague with the
world soon to follow!
I need to breathe.
I need to generate hormone.
Just a single breath.
Go, boy, and make for
the surface if you can.
I suffer not for want of air,
but my armor leaves me sorely
encumbered under the water.
A duel between heroes.
If you're lucky, you
can beat me to the top.
Come, you'll drown if you tarry.
act, and quickly.
Can I make it?
Will I just get dragged down to my doom?
I get one chance.
As death readied himself
for another victim,
Jojo felt a wellspring
of resolve burst forth.
His lungs screaming for breath,
an ordinary man would mindlessly
claw his way towards the surface.
But Jojo knew better than that.
Instead, he turned and swam
down, deeper into the abyss.
He's mad!
He's going deeper down!
What's this?
Danny's grabbed hold of your toy
pistol and won't give it back.
You're trying to take it away from him.
That's the reason.
Change your strategy.
Try giving it to him instead.
We're Night's Lot.
It's a coal mining town.
That means collapsed
tunnels and sunken earth.
There!
If I'm right, there should be air
trapped underneath these rocks!
I've found it!
With just one breath, my blood
is generating hormone again!
That's impossible!
Prepare yourself, servant of evil!
The tables have turned!
Down here, my hormone will
hit you all the harder!
Underwater...
Turquoise Blue Overdrive!
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out or not?
You spent the day your way.
Calling money while you feel the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out the lake.
Moms come out of the sky.
We stand there.
Why might I know we'll be there?
We'll see you!
Don't you say that we'll be there?
You'll be there too.
24 before I let you sing.
I'll be there with you.
Blufrid is a mess!
I just hit them until they fall to pieces!
This pain is nothing!
The day will come when this
will be the death of you.
Life magnetism!
Overdrive!